[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
I am old.
It's time to step down.
This position
will be passed on to Fixer Lunar.
Nobody should have a problem with that, right?
If there are any concerns, state them.
This is a chairpersons' meeting.
Why did you bring Fixer Solar in?
Here's the thing.
About the succession of Fixer Celestial,
I believe it is not your decision to make.
That is the tradition.
It is not your place to speak on this.
Fixer Celestial, I have always respected you.
However, we discovered
that the murder of Ching He's fixers
is connected to you.
So we must postpone handing over the position of Fixer Celestial
to your daughter.
All of you have discussed this
among yourselves, haven't you?
Do you really believe
that this matter
is related to me?
I know
you feel wronged.
Thackery Huang…
will never be
Ching He's
true master.
You are.
Dad.
You must take back the position
that belongs to you.
Only you
are qualified to be Fixer Celestial.
Make both sides of the law
fear you…
and respect you.
THE FIXERS
THE FIX
Is anyone home?
I'm back.
Lord Guan, I'm sorry.
Beside the lake, beneath the trees. I'll leave my money with you, praise be.
So much for their "buy one, get one free" sale.
I went all the way there, and then what?
I only got one bag.
Why did I even bother? Seriously.
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
Didn't you pray this morning?
Did you do something bad?
Prayer protects. Better safe than sorry.
That had better be the case.
Look.
You act all sneaky even when you're just on your phone.
Do you really have another woman?
Don't worry.
Nobody wants an old swamp eel like me.
You're my second, third, fourth, and fifth woman.
I can't escape from your grasp.
Look at your dad. Don't be like him.
All smooth and glib.
-Blah blah blah. -You chose him.
Did I raise you to talk back to me like this?
Welcome.
Hey, a good dog doesn't get in the way.
Hey, buddy.
This is for you.
I'm so sorry that I made you go on leave.
Consider this an apology.
Forgot me?
Scallion or pork floss?
He's treating you to a bun.
Scallion, of course. I like scallions.
You're too kind. Thanks.
Hey, I say, this partner of yours is quite weird.
Only weirdos can be partners with me.
Of course. You're so hard to get along with.
How's it with the police?
Welcome.
We need you to come down to the station to answer a few questions.
They have no evidence.
They can't do anything to me.
Glad you're okay. We're waiting for you to return.
Hey, all together.
I'm not going back.
I'm getting old, man.
Besides, I've made enough in the last few years. I'm set.
Can you really watch me paired up with this wily old fox?
Hey, listen.
You had it tough working with such a difficult partner.
He's just guarded.
He has a sharp tongue but a soft heart.
I know. A razor tongue, a heart like a girl.
Big nostrils, and eyes like pearls.
-If anything comes up, tell Ching He. -Okay.
Pay for yourself.
I'll charge you 40 for these two.
-Buddy. -This is 100.
Buddy, you don't have to do that. It's fine.
It's all right. No worries.
No worries.
You're back.
-We're home. -Give it to me.
Here, the backpack is so heavy.
Thank you.
-So heavy. -Let me see your hands.
How did anyone know that Fixer Shadow shot Noods?
I didn't report it. It's not me.
Fixer Expunge and Fixer Annul cleaned up the scene.
There shouldn't have been any trace.
Should we look into it?
No, I've already sent someone to handle it.
We have a tricky request this time.
The client is Hsiu of San He.
He is the right-hand man of San He's boss, Lin Wan-li.
Lin Wan-li has gone missing.
And someone saw
that Hsiu's men kidnapped him.
But Hsiu says that they didn't do it.
He suspects that Lin Kuei-pin is behind it all.
Did you know that San He's boss, Lin Wan-li, was kidnapped?
Yes.
I heard that it was Lin Wan-li's deputy, Hsiu.
If San He starts fighting amongst themselves,
do you know what to do next?
Do you mean his rival, Lin Kuei-pin?
Lin Wan-li is old.
Word is that two people in San He are gunning for the position.
One is Lin Wan-li's younger brother, Lin Kuei-pin.
Come on!
The other one is Hsiu.
Of the two, one is a hawk, and the other is a dove.
They always clash.
Why did you run up here?
All your brothers are down there.
Do you know what loyalty is?
If you sneak up here, how could you face your boss, Hsiu?
-After Lin Wan-li went missing… -Fuck!
…Lin Kuei-pin began making moves on Hsiu's turf.
He demands that he hand over his brother.
There's no way
the guy won't jump at the opportunity to make a move.
The current mayor's much-touted "city of happiness and excellence"
has become a breeding ground for organized crime.
A new headline for the reporters.
Shall we help push it along?
Tell your boss, Hsiu,
that I'll pay my respects every day until he hands over my brother.
Lin Kuei-pin!
Are you mad?
What are you doing here?
Don't you know what you did?
How could my men have touched Wan?
If you refuse to tell the truth,
there's nothing I can do.
Let's go!
After all, they're all part of San He.
Hsiu doesn't want both sides to suffer.
That's why Hsiu hired Ching He
to help find Lin Wan-li.
This can also prove that Lin Wan-li's disappearance
has nothing to do with him.
I'm not taking this case.
No fixer has ever dared refuse a case assigned by Ching He.
You used to be a member of San He.
You know how they work best.
Why won't you take it?
Anyway, I can't take this case.
Find someone else.
Have you forgotten the rules for fixers?
Don't worry.
We will handle it.
Why did you say no?
A personal grudge against San He?
That's my past. Don't ask.
Just like I don't ask about your business.
Got it?
TRUTH IS STRANGER THAN FICTION
Roses are red, violets are blue.
I'll take you down a peg or two.
Cocky, eh?
A master of pen and sword.
Out of everyone in San He, you're the most cultured.
I, Chen Liang-chi,
was supposed to wield a pen.
Now I'm wielding a gun.
That's why
I'm going to send my daughter abroad for school
so she can see the world for me.
Nice.
-Your turn. -I'll go.
"Violets."
"Are."
"Blue."
Holy crap.
Two years of practice beaten in two months.
Did you dope?
This is nothing. Give me two more months.
I'll even be able to hit a fly, I tell you.
Goodness, that's incredible.
Okay, one day,
we'll have you perform fly-shooting for Wan.
You'll rise through the ranks.
The first boss to rise to power by shooting flies.
Fall, leaves, fall; die, flowers, away.
"Fall."
Rise to power making flies my prey.
Come on, Boss Fly.
NOTHING IS SO BEAUTIFUL AS SPRING
SPRING
Looking for me?
What have you been up to lately?
Being the youngest son of a political dynasty,
who is very obedient to his dad
and keeps a very low profile.
What kind of attitude is that?
How could you talk to Dad like that?
What's wrong?
You're coming to our family's ancestral worship this year.
Every major media outlet will be there.
Learn from your brother how to handle them.
Learn more from him, understand?
Be his lackey?
You are part of the Hsueh family.
Stop idling around all day.
You still remember that I'm a Hsueh?
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen with me?
Just do as I say.
If you really don't want to go,
then don't!
Dad only did this because he wants to patch things up with you.
No matter what I do, I will never become a good son to him.
Don't let me drag you into this.
Haven't you always wanted his approval?
Dad has always hoped you could come home and help.
I do too.
I need someone whom I can truly trust to help me.
You are incredibly adept
at reading power dynamics.
I need your advice.
I also want to show Dad what you're capable of.
DADDY NOT HERE?
ARE YOU ALONE?
Sorry.
Sorry for making you wait. I was tidying up in the back.
Exactly 100 dollars.
It's rather late, so there are discounts.
Thank you.
You have a good child.
You're back.
I'm back.
DADDY NOT HERE? ARE YOU ALONE?
THE WAY OF THREE HARMONIES
Don't let anyone else know that I'm meeting with you, officer.
After all, it's tricky given who we are.
I understand.
Has Lin Wan-li made any enemies recently?
DETECTIVE
He is nearing retirement. He values harmony above all else.
He's unlikely to have conflicts with anyone.
In fact, Wan has already made arrangements.
He knew he was getting on in years.
He wrote his will a while ago.
Word is that
Lin Wan-li's abduction
is connected to Lin Kuei-pin and Hsiu.
Impossible.
One is his younger brother.
-And he practically raised Hsiu. -Yu.
I heard that the police came by.
How come you didn't tell me?
I didn't have time to tell you.
Officer,
what do you want to know?
Pin, the police came to help find your brother.
Which unit are you from?
Who sent you here?
Wan? Wan, is it you?
What is that sound? Hello?
Put it on speaker.
Wan?
-Wan? -In three days. On a bus.
The ransom is one million.
Only Lin Wan-li's wife can board the bus.
If we see that someone is following, we will kill him at once.
Hey, can you let me--
Did I hear that correctly?
A ransom of one million dollars?
Motherfucker!
Are they insulting us?
We suggest that you do not act yet.
Let the police handle it.
This is a family matter. We've got it.
-We don't need the police. -Pin.
You're only putting him in more danger this way.
See him out!
Officer, please.
HUNG HSING BAKERY
Strange. Why did he close so early?
He didn't put things away.
HU TUNG-YU, FIXER SHADOW, AGE 43
STATUS: DECEASED
Fixer Terra, what brings you here?
Some things are better said in person.
As your old friend,
I have to warn you about something.
Do you want to talk to me
about the recent rumors
that Ching He
leaked our secrets
to the police
and even tried to eliminate our own fixers?
It's not just us who know the news.
Our clients know too.
Several clients wanted to hire us.
But they all backed out suddenly in the last few days.
Someone is obviously behind the rumors.
Why should we throw ourselves into a panic?
If clients feel that Ching He cannot guard their secrets,
they could turn on Ching He at any time.
Three men make a tiger.
A lie told often enough becomes the truth.
Don't forget.
Some people try to get back what they lost
the same way it was taken from them.
Sir,
Tristan's support has been growing lately.
Becoming mayor
is well within reach.
Thanks to you, Madam Fan.
We are grateful for everything Yeh Yueh Tong has done.
It's you who gave Yeh Yueh Tong the chance to prove
that Yeh Yueh Tong can do
anything Ching He can do.
And we can do it better.
I heard that Ching He has been having some trouble lately.
The way Thackery Huang works will only harm Ching He.
If Ching He's legacy is to continue,
it needs a better leader.
It seems like
you have some ideas.
Ching He Temple is the central hub of the organization.
Staying neutral is a thing of the past.
Ching He now needs someone in the dark
and someone in the light.
No one is more qualified than the Hsueh family to be in the light.
As for the dark side, leave it to me.
As long as we join forces,
we hold all the cards.
You want to take over Ching He?
I only want to reclaim my rightful position.
I see.
How about this?
Give me one week.
By then,
I will have a satisfactory answer for everyone.
Here.
We haven't played chess in ages.
Let's play a game. What do you say?
Maybe next time.
I have other plans.
I have a feeling that we will meet again very soon.
Looks like it's not just Fixer Terra.
Fixers Earth, Arcane, Cosmos, and Eon are also concerned.
Now that management knows,
we need to clean up this mess fast.
Invite Hsiu here.
Tell him we won't charge for the job.
However,
we hope San He can do something for Ching He.
If you fail to take over Ching He
and Ching He turns on you…
That's no small risk.
Sir, do you know
that Ching He Temple houses
a set of classified files that could shake things up at home and abroad?
I have heard of that.
It's the cornerstone
that has allowed Ching He to remain neutral all these years.
These classified files do exist.
They're called the Primordial Files.
Fixer Primordium
was the greatest fixer in Ching He's history.
They handled the most difficult classified jobs.
Only the heads of Ching He know where the files are.
However, Thackery Huang doesn't,
while I do.
If I have your support in dealing with Thackery Huang,
we will be able to control both sides of the law.
I will be your most powerful ally.
This bridge
connects two sides of the city.
One side symbolizes order and power.
The other,
opportunity and ambition.
It's not opposition…
but symbiosis.
THREE-IN-ONE COMBO, AMAZING VALUE
TWENTY MILLION DOLLARS ONLY
I don't know if your husband ever told you about my job.
He took out a life insurance policy with our company.
He left it to you and your child.
We hope this helps during this difficult time.
He was always like this.
Refusing to tell me anything.
Shouldering everything on his own.
I don't want this money.
I just want him back.
Our condolences.
I know
this isn't an insurance payout.
Thank you.
I'm very sorry.
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't shot and injured him,
he wouldn't have died.
Stop flattering yourself.
Being a fixer has its risks.
That's the price he paid for doing this job.
We've laid Fixer Shadow to rest.
Fixer Expunge and the others will handle the rest.
Haven't we already wrapped things up?
When a fixer dies,
their partner will bring their body back.
Fixer Expunge will erase all records
that tie them to Ching He.
It's just that some memories can't be erased.
STIR-FRIED SWAMP EEL
By the way, how is the San He case going?
Didn't you say you don't care about San He?
I don't, but I have to mind my partner's business, right?
I injured my hand during the mission that day.
It'll be fine in a few days.
Lin Kuei-pin keeps hounding Hsiu.
He will definitely do something before the ransom is paid.
This gang conflict fully exposes our current mayor's incompetence.
The city of happiness has turned into a city of gangsters.
Mayor, please come forward and apologize to our citizens.
Fuck you, Lin Kuei-pin!
TRAITOR
Don't neglect your duties
just because you are stepping down.
Please continue to safeguard our citizens.
I told you to wear a disguise. Why are you dressed for fishing?
If you're gonna do it, do it with some heart.
Make the villains take the bait.
Got it?
Look at you wearing shades at night.
Are you sure you can see?
Not again.
What's the deal now?
Is Yeh Yueh Tong butting into all of Ching He's cases now?
We have a common target, Lin Wan-li.
It has nothing to do with Yeh Yueh Tong.
We're cooperating this time.
No objections, right?
-Fine by me. -Who's asking you?
-Hello? -Did you bring the money?
I'm here to collect it now.
Where are you?
At the next stop,
toss the money out the back door.
Don't get off the bus.
If you miss the stop, your husband will die.
Motherfucker, stop!
No need to chase.
I placed a tracker in the bag.
Hey. We did it!
-What? -We've got a million!
You got it? Where? Show me.
Damn, thank goodness I ran fast,
or I would've been killed.
Take this plate of roast duck and pay respects to our God of Wealth.
God of Wealth, time to eat.
No need to tempt me like this.
I already saw your face.
Who are you kidding? How could you?
Well, I can see my asshole.
Did you dye your hair straw-colored?
-Hey, he saw me! Hey! -What's wrong?
What is it?
-He saw me. -He saw you?
I told you not to use a trash bag.
Never kidnapped anyone before, right?
You only asked San He for one million?
Are you looking down on me
or San He?
-San He? -Hey, what's San He?
How would I know? Don't you know? What's San He?
Lin Wan-li.
You have a phone, right?
-Who is Lin Wan-li? -Google it.
Well? Is he?
-Yes. -Is it him? It's him.
What do we do now?
Fuck, it's your fault. Why San He of all people?
All right, be quiet!
I will figure it out.
Haven't we always been like this?
You and I, brawn and brains.
I'm hungry.
If you feed me well,
I won't rat you out.
He's hungry. What should we do?
Sir, have a duck leg.
What's the deal with you two?
How did you end up resorting to kidnapping?
We lost money playing Texas Hold'em and are drowning in debt.
If we don't pay it off,
we'll lose the rest of our fingers.
How long have you two known each other?
We've been hanging out since we were kids.
We're buddies.
Watching you two
reminds me of two young lads who used to follow me around.
They were very much like you.
But they were smarter.
And more shrewd.
In my whole life, I've never seen anyone
as stupid as you two.
He's talking about you, stupid.
Looking back, the days when those two lads followed me around
were the happiest times of my life.
Was it only my wife who spoke to you guys?
What about other gang leaders?
No.
Tomorrow, I'll head down the mountain
and tell them that I staged everything.
This way, you'll be fine.
Then go pay off your gambling debts.
After that is settled,
come work for me.
Okay.
Boss! Hey, call him boss.
-Boss. -Boss.
Reporting, boss.
Nature calls. I'm going to take a leak.
Go on.
Come, sit.
Hold on.
Who sent you to rescue me?
Who sent you to kill me?
Wan, the crew has come to send you off.
Pin?
That coward.
He wants to kill me
but is afraid to do it himself?
I'm very sorry.
Sharing this meal with you guys
has made me very happy.
Wan-li,
sorry.
Lin Wan-li.
I never thought
we would meet again under these circumstances.
Hang in there.
Wan will be here soon.
Hang in there. It'll be fine.
Hang in there, you hear me?
Hurry and go.
Wan and the others aren't coming.
Hello?
Hello, Fixer Lucky?
Where are you guys?
Do you remember the rule I told you?
When a fixer dies…
their partner has to collect their body.
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu